Finding Aid for Lisa Marshall Bashert Papers, 1971-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Lisa Marshall Bashert Papers, 1971-2010
Bashert, Lisa Marshall
6 linear feet
0526 Aa 2
Lisa Marshall Bashert is a lesbian feminist witch from Ypsilanti, Michigan. She was involved in various causes and local organizations, especially relating to gay-lesbian activism in Michigan. She is a graduate of the University of Michigan and a life-partner of Beth Bashert. The Bashert collection consists almost entirely of her journals which are a combination of diaries, musings and other personal reflections about such topics as her sexuality, her personal relationships, and her involvement in feminist, lesbian, and pagan organizations.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Lisa Marshall Bashert (donor no. 9510 ) and came to the library in September 2004. Several additions to the collection have been received.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open only with the written permission of Lisa Marshall Bashert. The collection will be open without restriction upon her death.
Lisa Marshall Bashert is a lesbian feminist witch from Ypsilanti, Michigan. She was involved in various causes and local organizations, especially relating to gay-lesbian activism in Michigan. She is a graduate of the University of Michigan and a life-partner of Beth Bashert.
The Bashert collection consists almost entirely of her journals which are a combination of diaries, musings and other personal reflections about such topics as her sexuality, her personal relationship, and her involvement in feminist, lesbian, and pagan organizations.
Subjects:
Bashert, Lisa Marshall.; Bashert, Beth.; Coming out (sexual orientation); Feminists--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Gays--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Lesbians--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Witchcraft--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; New Age movement.; Ypsilanti (Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Diaries.
- Journals
  (also includes programs, writings, published materials, letters written, notes on classes taken, personal reflections, etc.)
  - 1971-1990 (Box 1)
  - 1990-1993 (Box 2)
  - 1996-1999 (Box 3)
  - 2000-2005 (Box 4)
  - 1994-2005, 16 folders (Box 5)
    (includes loose materials from journals)
  - 2006, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - 2007-2010, 12 folders (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous
  - Rainbow Neighbors, 1999-2000 (Box 6)
  - CD-ROM copy of Bashert journals, 1998-2004 (Box 6)